<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>startups by day, standup by night on Isaac Tay - Startups by Day, Standup by Night</title>
    <link>https://www.isaactay.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in startups by day, standup by night on Isaac Tay - Startups by Day, Standup by Night</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Isaac Tay</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.isaactay.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First smart contract deployed</title>
      <link>https://www.isaactay.com/post/2022-02-02-first-smart-contract/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaactay.com/post/2022-02-02-first-smart-contract/</guid>
      <description>Deployed my first smart contract on 10 October 2021 on the Binance Smart Chain. Contract is based on the ERC721 standard and to help solve the problem of tracking lineage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts on LinkedIn about Talent</title>
      <link>https://www.isaactay.com/post/2022-02-02-linkedin-posts-related-to-talent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaactay.com/post/2022-02-02-linkedin-posts-related-to-talent/</guid>
      <description>A series of posts on LinkedIn on the challenges faced in a competitive landscape to establish the supply lines for talent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get with the Program @ The Merry Lion</title>
      <link>https://www.isaactay.com/show/2019-10-26-the-merry-lion-get-with-the-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaactay.com/show/2019-10-26-the-merry-lion-get-with-the-program/</guid>
      <description>First hour-long show. Pretty excited about this milestone. First time on stage was in June 2013 at Comedy Masala. I took a break performing regularly in 2015 after honestbee was started. Kickstarted the standup comedy journey again after leaving the company. It has been an emotional rollercoaster these twelve months and part of that experience will be seeping into the set.
Startups by Day, Standup by Night. Suaku, Kiasu, Kaisee - in 2019, Isaac travelled from Singapore to London by land on buses and trains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isaac Tay - a longer introduction.</title>
      <link>https://www.isaactay.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaactay.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I do product management during the day and perform standup comedy at night. I work with product managers, data scientists, designers, marketers, business development executives, and engineers to deliver the right product to the right users at the right time.
I was one of the three co-founders of honestbee. I left in 2018 to pursue my own path. In her halycon days, honestbee was in eight markets - Singapore, Malaysia, Thailand, Philippines, Indonesia, Japan, Taiwan, Hong Kong - delivering food and groceries to customers that loved her service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Right Answers with Host Sam See!</title>
      <link>https://www.isaactay.com/show/2021-01-19-no-right-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaactay.com/show/2021-01-19-no-right-answers/</guid>
      <description>First time doing a quiz show on Twitch. Will be competing with David Rose from Australia and the Maldivian Nuha.
As a Singaporean mugger road, I&amp;rsquo;m deeply uncomfortable with not knowing how to prepare for this quiz. Sam&amp;rsquo;s not helping kelong either. :-(</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>